https://bluesfestivalguide.com/privacy-policy/

Blues Festival Guide Magazine and Online Directory of Blues Festivals
Privacy Policy - Blues Festival Guide Magazine and Online Directory of Blues Festivals
Latest News
Josh Smith “Voted as one of the top 20 Best Living Blues Guitar Players by Guitar World Magazine”
Texas Blues Rocker Clay Melton Releasing Guitar-Driven
Live Performance Video
Crescent City Blues & BBQ Festival “Festing in Place” October 16-15, 2020
Congratulations to our 2nd winner in the One-on-One contest, John Eric Adams of Fernandina Beach, FL
Homebound Bender
Win a One-on One “Live” Video Experience
The Jimmys ::
GOTTA HAVE IT feat. “Write A Hit”
Read all 60 pages of the 2020 Blues Festival Guide Digital Mag — Now Live
Blues Festival Guide Magazine Media Platforms Feature Livestreams & Online Concerts & more
Mike Zito’s Quarantine Blues is the Band’s Gift
Mississippi’s Cathead Distillery Donates Hand Sanitizer to Blues Artists in Poverty
Twitter
Search for:
Click for E-Guide Advertising Info
~ Privacy Policy ~
RBA Publishing
We respect your privacy, and we do not share your information with third parties for marketing or advertising purposes.
Information We Collect
When you browse our Web site, our Web server does not automatically record information regarding your domain, URL, IP address or similar information.
Uses
The information we collect through our online posting forms is not shared with other organizations for marketing purposes – information is solely used by RBA Publishing. For all our forms such as “Submit Festival”, “Post Link”, and “Become Distributor” forms, all personal contact information is not published, shared or sold to any 3rd party; only the information that you request to publicize your business will be published.
We may use personal information to contact you regarding advertising in our print magazine and/or online.
Cookies
We do not use cookies.
Ad Servers
We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies (other companies that place their ads on Web pages).
Effective Date
The effective date of this Privacy Policy is January 1, 2002.
Changes
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes, and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Security
We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
HOME PAGE Copyright 2020.
